Finding Aid for the William and Lee Bell Scripts for Television Soap Operas PASC.0096
UCLA Library Special Collections
- YOUNG AND THE RESTLESS, THE
  - Prod. #5746-5752. Aired: 11/21/95-11/02/95. (Box 738)
  - Prod. #5753-5759. Aired: 12/01/95-12/12/95. (Box 739)
  - Prod. #5760-5767. Aired: 12/12/95-12/21/95. (Box 740)
  - Prod. #5768-5774. Aired: 12/22/95-01/02/96. (Box 741)
  - Prod. #5775-5780. Aired: 01/03/96-01/10/96. (Box 742)
  - Prod. #5781-5788. Aired: 12/12/95-01/22/96. (Box 743)
  - Prod. #5789-5798. Aired: 01/23/96-02/01/96. (Box 744)
  - Prod. #5797-5804. Aired: 02/01/96-02/13/96. (Box 745)
  - Prod. #5805-5812. Aired: 02/14/96-02/23/96. (Box 746)
  - Prod. #5813-5821. Aired: 02/26/96-03/07/96. (Box 747)
  - Prod. #5822-5829. Aired: 03/08/96-03/21/96. (Box 748)
  - Prod. #5830-5839. Aired: 03/22/96-04/04/96. (Box 749)
  - Prod. #5840-5847. Aired: 04/05/96-04/16/96. (Box 750)
  - Prod. #5855-5860. Aired: 04/26/96-4/3/96. (Box 751)
  - Prod. #5854-5848. Aired: 04/2/96-04/17/96. (Box 752)
  - Prod. #5861-5868. Aired: 05/06/96-05/15/96. (Box 754)
  - Prod. #5869-5876. Aired: 05/16/96-05/24/96. (Box 755)
  - Prod. #5877-5883. Aired: 05/27/96-06/04/96. (Box 756)
  - Prod. #5884-5890. Aired: 06/06/96-06/13/96. (Box 757)
  - Prod. #5891-5897. Aired: 06/14/96-06/24/96. (Box 758)
  - Prod. #5898-5905. Aired: 06/25/96-07/04/96. (Box 759)
  - Prod. #5906-5913. Aired: 07/05/96-07/16/96. (Box 760)
  - Prod. #5914-5921. Aired: 07/17/96-07/26/96. (Box 761)
  - Prod. #5922-5929. Aired: 07/29/96-08/07/96. (Box 762)
  - Prod. #5930-5938. Aired: 08/08/96-08/20/96. (Box 763)
  - Prod. #5939-5946. Aired: 08/21/96-08/30/96. (Box 764)
  - Prod. #5947-5953. Aired: 09/03/96-09/12/96. (Box 765)
  - Prod. #5954-5960. Aired: 09/13/96-09/23/96. (Box 766)
  - Prod. #5961-5968. Aired: 09/24/96-10/3/96. (Box 767)
  - Prod. #5969-5976. Aired: 10/04/96-10/15/96. (Box 768)
  - Prod. #5977-5984. Aired: 10/16/96-10/25/96. (Box 769)
  - Prod. #5985-5991. Aired: 0/28/96-11/05/96. (Box 770)
  - Prod. #5992-5998. Aired: 11/06/96-11/14/96. (Box 771)
  - Prod. #5999-6006. Aired: 11/15/96-11/26/96. (Box 772)
  - Prod. #6007-6013. Aired: 11/27/96-12/06/96. (Box 773)
  - Prod. #6014-6021. Aired: 12/09/96-12/18/96. Notes: #6017 missing. (Box 774)
  - Prod. #6022-6028. Aired: 12/19/96-12/27/96. (Box 775)
  - Prod. #6029-6035. Aired: 12/30/96-01/08/97. (Box 776)
  - Prod. #6036-6044. Aired: 01/09/97-01/21/97. (Box 777)
  - Prod. #6045-6048. Aired: 01-22/96-01/28/97. (Box 778)
  - Prod. #6049-6055. Aired: 01/29/97-02/06/97. (Box 779)
  - Prod. #6056-6062. Aired: 02/07/97-02/17/97. (Box 780)
  - Prod. #6063-6069. Aired: 02/18/97-02/26/97. (Box 781)
  - Prod. #6070-6076. Aired: 02/27/9703/07/97. (Box 782)
  - Prod. #6084-6090. Aired: 03/21/97-03/31/97. (Box 784)
  - Prod. #6091-6097. Aired: 04/01/97-04/09/97. (Box 785)
  - Prod. #6098-6104. Aired: 04/10/97-04/18/97. (Box 786)
  - Prod. #6105-6111. Aired: 04/21/97-04/29/97. (Box 787)
  - Prod. #6112-6118. Aired: 04/30/97-05/08/97. (Box 788)
  - Prod. #6119-6125. Aired: 05/09/97-05/19/97. (Box 789)
  - Prod. #6126-6131. Aired: 05/20/97-05/27/97. (Box 790)
  - Prod. #6132-6138. Aired: 05/28/97-06/05/97. (Box 791)
  - Prod. #6139-6145. Aired: 06/06/97-06/16/97. (Box 792)
  - Prod. #6146-6152. Aired: 06/07/97-06/25/97. (Box 793)
  - Prod. #6154-6159. Aired: 06/26/97-07/04/97. (Box 794)
  - Prod. #6160-6166. Aired: 07/07/97-07/15/97. (Box 795)
  - Prod. #6167-6174. Aired: 07/16/97-07/25/97. (Box 796)
  - Prod. #6175-6181. Aired: 07/28/97-08/05/97. (Box 797)
  - Prod. #6182-6188. Aired: 08/06/97-08/14/97. (Box 798)
  - Prod. #6189-6195. Aired: 08/15/97-08/25/97. (Box 799)
  - Prod. #6196-6201. Aired: 08/26/97-09/03/97. (Box 800)
  - Prod. #6202-6208. Aired: 09/04/97-09/15/97. (Box 801)
  - Prod. #6209-6214. Aired: 09/16/97-09/23/97. (Box 802)
  - Prod. #6215-6221. Aired: 09/24/97-10/02/97. (Box 803)
  - Prod. #6222-6227. Aired: 10/03/97-10/10/97. (Box 804)
  - Prod. #6228-6233. Aired: 10/13/97-10/20/97. (Box 805)
  - Prod. #6234-6237. Aired: 10/21/97-10/24/97. (Box 806)
- YOUNG AND THE RESTLESS,THE
  - Prod. #6077-6083. Aired: 03/10/97-03/20/97. (Box 783)